mumzworld.com 2015-12-20

# Privacy Policy

Mumzworld.com (from here on referred to as ‘we’, ‘our’, ‘us’) is committed to protecting the privacy of every one of our customers. We are always here to answer your questions about the privacy of the personal information you register with us and we obtain by other means and how we use and share it. Just call our [Customer Service Helpline](http://www.mumzworld.com/en/contact-us) or [email](mailto:support@mumzworld.com) our customer care team if you have any questions or concerns that haven’t been answered by this document.

**How we use your information**

We only use your information to carry out your order and send you specially selected emails about deals that we think will interest you. We don’t sell your information to any third party organizations and only share it with our trusted partners who help make your experience on mumzworld what it is. It is our responsibility to protect your personal information from unauthorized access by third parties. **The details collected from you do not include your credit card details.**

**How we obtain your information**

We collect a combination of personal and statistical information about everyone who uses our site- whether or not you are a registered user. We store all your information with utmost attention to privacy and security. We also comply with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards, which means we regularly assess the vulnerability of all our IP addresses to external interference and we use Secure Socket Layers (SSLs), which encrypt data when you log in or make a payment.

Personal Information we require 

All our registered users are asked to provide us with the following personal details:

  * Full Name
  * Email address
  * Contact Number
  * Billing Address
  * Shipping Address(es)
  * Name/ Date of birth/ Gender of Child/ Children (if applicable)

Please note that any credit card details collected from you will not be stored, sold, leased, rented or shared to any third parties. This information is not even available to our staff, even if we wanted access to it. In addition, your credit card transaction is managed by trusted, certified and legally authorized partners that ensure your credit card information is always secure during every transaction. We also store all personal details provided to us by non-registered users and use it in the same way we use the information provided to us by registered users. 

Other information we might collect

Mumzworld and our third party partners, for example advertisers and content providers, may also collect statistical information about you while you use our site. Statistical information that we gather may include where a user is and on the Internet (e.g. the URL that they last came from, the computer’s IP address and the domain types like .com and .ae that the user uses), browser type, which language content is being viewed in, the country and telephone area code where the computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during the visit, the advertisements that were clicked on and any search terms that were entered on our website. We do not use this information to identify you personally and we may collect it even if you are not a registered mumzworld user.

We also record all telephone calls and save all email contact that our customers have with mumzworld. This is for the purpose of quality control and the development of our services- but we may also collect additional personal data and information from your telephone calls and emails.

Cookies

Cookies are small text files that gather information about non- personally identifiable visitors to websites. IP and ULR addresses are gathered through the use of Cookies- as well as the date and time of a visit to our site. Cookies help customize your Internet experience, and are used on most commercial sites. They allow us to help bring you the offers, advertisements and features that are most relevant to you and allow you to save personal details on your browser, such as your password, which will be accessible next time you visit our site. You can adjust your browser to alert you when a website is trying to send you cookies and also to block all cookies whilst visiting our site. Blocking cookies will mean that you are only able to use mumzworld for the purpose of browsing and research rather than purchasing products. Through the use of cookies, we can track previous websites that our visitors and other users of the IP address have been to as well as the search terms entered by users. Cookies are used purely for the purpose of statistical analysis of traffic flows for the improvement of our website, and are **never stored in a form in which individual users can be identified**. Therefore, they are not used to collect personal information about you. The statistical data collected as a result of Cookies is not transferred to our third party partners in a form that discloses any of your personal details in connection with them.  Please be aware that our providers of advertising and content on our site may also use cookies to collect data about traffic flows themselves. We make sure that all our partners follow stringent security and privacy procedures.

Google

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

Google services implemented on Mumzworld:

      • Remarketing with Google AdSense

      • Google Display Network Impression Reporting

      • Demographics and Interests Reporting

      • DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

**Why we collect this information**

We collect this information so we can personalize your shopping experience and make sure you can easily find what you really want and need. We also use it to process your orders efficiently and accurately (i.e. we might have to call you to confirm an address), for statistical and survey purposes, to make sure you’re included when we consider making site changes and/or adding new product lines and ensure the web content advertisements appearing on your screen are specially tailored to your needs. We will only contact you by email about special offers and deals with your prior consent.

We use cookies to assess which advertisements you access and which areas of the site are viewed the most. By measuring traffic flow in this way, we can assess our most popular features as well as areas that need improvement. We do not store any information from cookies for longer than your session on our site lasts, although you can chose to store information by _saving your trolley_ or password.

**Who do we share your information with?**

We share your personally identifiable information with the reputable third parties who help process your order, such as delivery and logistics teams and payment processing agencies. All of the third parties that work together with in processing your order have stringent confidentially and security measures and are committed to preventing the misuse of your personal information. We also reserve the right to share your personal details if we believe it is necessary to comply with the law, to protect the safety of mumzworld or the safety of our users or to protect mumzworld property rights.

We may share non-personally identifiable information, such as your URL or IP address with third party advertisers or third party advertising companies. This information CANNOT be traced to your personal details.

**Your Product Reviews**

You can chose to add product reviews and you may be asked to contribute them after purchasing an item, this is an optional rather than obligatory part of being a mumzworld registered user. Your product reviews may be used in mumzworld marketing and/or promotional material and or that of the manufacturer of the reviewed product and/or any of our partner companies who we work with to serve customers. You have the right to have your review removed at any time, in this event you should send our customer service team your request by [email](mailto:support@mumzworld.com). You have the option to can submit reviews anonymously.

**Mumzworld Community**

As with product reviews, your comments and contributions to the mumzworld community may be used by mumzworld in its marketing and/or promotional material as well as that of any of our featured brands, manufacturers or merchants. Your comments and contributions may also be used in the marketing/ promotional material of any of our partner companies with whom we work to serve customers. You have the option of contributing to the mumzworld community anonymously.

**Information Security**

The security of your personal details is of utmost importance to us and we employ stringent security measures to make sure that your details cannot be accessed by third parties who we do not already have a trusted relationship and agreement with. We comply with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards, which means we regularly assess the vulnerability of all our IP addresses to external interference and we use Secure Socket Layers (SSLs), which encrypt data when you log in or make a payment.

**Your information, your rights**

You have the right to view all and any part of the personally identifiable information we keep about you if you inform us of your request in writing. Just contact us at [support@mumzworld.com](mailto:support@mumzworld.com) and request us to provide you with all the personally identifiable information that we store about you. You also have the right to change all personally identifiable information that we keep on our records. See the following paragraph for more details.

**Changing your personal information on mumzworld**

Once you change or revise your personal information on mumzworld, we will only contact or refer to you by the newest information that you have provided. Because we make periodic back-ups of information, we may not be able to completely delete your former details, but we will not use them for any promotional and/or customer contact reasons.

To change or revise any of the personal information we hold about you, just drop us an [email](mailto:support@mumzworld.com).

**Conditions of Use**

By joining and/or using mumzworld, you confirm that you do not consider the stated Privacy policies a breach of your rights. Please note that our Privacy Policy is periodically updated and that users are bound by the most recent update of the policy. It is therefore the customer/user’s responsibility to continue to check our Privacy Policy for updates. By registering for a mumzworld account, you also confirm that you do not object to us contacting you via any of the contact details that you provided us with upon registration or after registration. Please

**Opting Out**

Mumzworld users are given the option of registering for our newsletter and other news about special offers and deals. If, at any time, you prefer not to receive email marketing information from us please follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email OR contact us at [support@mumzworld.com](mailto:support@mumzworld.com) and instruct us to remove your email address from our database. For us to be able to do so, please include your email address in the body of your email and write "Unsubscribe" in the subject line." We will process your request as soon as we can. In this way you are modifying your mumzworld account settings, rather than cancelling your membership.

If you wish to cancel your mumzworld account, please send our Customer Services department an email - with the words ‘Cancel Account’ in the title. Your account will be cancelled and we will delete all personal details that we have stored about you within 28 days. However, we are not responsible for contacting and/ or deleting the personal details about you that we have shared with our trusted partners.

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the [Google Analytics Opt Out Browser](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) add on.

**Contact Information**

mumzworld.com  
Dubai Internet City  
Building 10, Office 306  
PO Box 500245  
Dubai UAE

Telephone: +971 4 433 9460

*Office Hours: 9 AM - 7 PM (UAE time)
